Aaron Hannah Shakespeare

SKILLS

Transitioning from the fast-paced world of fashion to the dynamic realm of technology has been a natural progression in fulfilling my interests.

As I commit to continuous learning as a programmer, I find motivation through the satisfaction of understanding new tools, concepts and problem solving.

EXPERIENCE

Self Employed, Worldwide — Fashion Model

March 2017 - PRESENT

- Liaising with agencies and clients in various countries.
- Learning basics of new languages to help bridge language barriers.
- Planning travel and accommodation.
- Working on projects with large new teams, understanding client needs and project objectives.
- Sustaining mental and physical performance for extended hours.
- Upholding embargo and NDA.

Femme Fatale Tattoo, London — *Personal/General/Studio Assistant*

June 2022 - October 2022

- Coordinating with external partners to facilitate stock delivery and maintain optimal inventory levels.
- Creating social media content and responding to enquiries.
- Validating age and consent forms.

EDUCATION

Just IT, London — *Software Skills*

April 2024 - June 2024

A three month bootcamp, during which I was able to learn new language skills and refine concepts learnt from self-study.

New City College (Epping Forest College), Essex — BTEC

2012

Performing Arts & Dance | Distinction - Distinction - Distinction

Roding Valley High School, Essex — *GCSE*

2008

English – B | Maths – C | Science – C | Total - 12